# **Prateek Rathore**

FullStack Developer with 5 years experience

(91) 95270-53469

<u>p.rathore.2903@gmail.com</u> prateekrathore.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**FIGmd (India) Pvt. Ltd,** Pune — *Software Developer* (Joined Krixi solutions before merger)

() carrow remain contactions contact

March 2017 - Present

**Keriton**, Philadelphia (Remotely) — *Software Engineer* 

September 2016 - Feb 2017

**Consistenza Technologies**, Pune — Mobile App Developer

July 2015 - August 2016

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Jaipur Institute of Eng. & Tech.**, Jaipur — B. Tech

2010 - 2014

Rajasthan Technical University

#### **COURSES**

## **UX Designing**, Felix IT Pune

March 2018 - June 2018

### **OPEN SOURCE CONTRIBUTION**

# rn-responsive-font

Magical & easy method for responsive font size based on screen width to support all size devices.

# @and rocons is/react-native-json schema-form

A React-Native component to build React-Native forms out of jsonschema

#### **SKILLS**

ReactJS, React-Native, Android Native Development & iOS Native Development NodeJS, MongoDB

Chrome Developer Tools, Jest, E2E testing

JSDOC, Python, Web Scraping

#### **ABOUT ME**

Over the span of time, I have designed, implemented, integrated, developed and tested various impactful applications in diverse, collaborative environments. In the last few months I have been focusing on using best practices in my code. I am fascinated by User Experience Design. In my leisure time, I like to read blogs, listen to Music, and play Guitar. I have recently deployed my Personal website prateekrathore.com built with Gatsby.js & ReactJS...

#### **PROJECTS**

## **Pegasus PRO** — Web App

PRO stands for Patient Reported Outcome. The module presents aggregated data of the recorded responses using various graphs, charts, and grids. While leading the UI team, Define code practices to build a decoupled code-base minimizing code smells. I handle the front end and a couple of microservices working on NodeJS, GraphQL & MongoDB.

## **Graft** — Android & iOS

GRAFT collects patient demographics, procedural variables and outcomes information at baseline and follow-up time points. This app can be used by only registered members to enter data into The Plastic Surgery Foundation's General Registry of Autologous Fat Transfer (GRAFT).

## Holiday Ambassador — <u>Android</u> & <u>iOS</u>

Holiday Ambassador is an enterprise app. The App lists packages & Campaigns, User can generate leads for Makemytrip(online travel company). User can share packages & campaigns on other apps. Implemented push notifications.

## 8 Regina — Android & iOS

This is a classic 8 queen puzzle game app. The aim is to place 8 queens on a chess board without threatening each other! Simply tap on a square to place the queen and tap again to remove her!

# Techgium — <u>Android</u> & <u>iOS</u>

Techgium is an information application which gives you detailed information of what Techgium is & how you can enroll with it. Built with IONIC v1 & seamless animations.

# Kare Nurse App — <u>iOS</u>

Kare Nurse App is a Milk Management System Solution for Neonatal ICUs to improve nurse productivity. App handles various Activities and Validations that nurses had to perform manually. I was part of lean team developing 2 apps with IONIC v1. App handles various Business Checks, fits Hipaa Compliance. I coded to produce intuitive and simple-to-use applications to improve NICU experiences.

# **Taj Business Partner App** — *Android*

Taj Business Partner Application provides a platform to add Potential Customer Details in there Taj Business Partner Account. App also has registration and login process. Uploading Images from Mobile. Taj Business Partner App is developed using React-Native.

Other Apps: COMMUMART, VIBGYOR, POWERHOUSE GYM TRAINERS, VOICE HOUSE, K11, Lokal App